The battle for mankind will not be on earth
AE: Apocalypse Earth is a tv movie, science
fiction film directed by Thunder Levin.
A group of refugees from Earth land on an exotic planet, where
they must fight ruthless aliens to survive.
Lt. Frank Baum, played by Adrian Paul.
Capt. Sam Crowe, played by Richard Grieco.
Lea, played by Bali Rodriguez.
Tim, played by Gray Hawks.
Sgt. Peebles, played by Jay Cardell.
Colin, played by Daniel Ross Mix.
AE: Apocalypse Earth is a 2013 American science fiction film produced by The Asylum, directed
by Thunder Levin and Agung Bagus, starring Adrian Paul and Richard Grieco.
It is a mockbuster of After Earth and Oblivion.
The tone is thought_provoking.